(gentle music swells)
♪ It's always around me,
all this noise, but ♪
♪ Not nearly as loud as the voice saying ♪
♪ "Let it happen, let it happen" ♪
♪ It's gonna feel so good ♪
♪ "Just let it happen, let it happen" ♪
♪ All this running around ♪
♪ Tryin' to cover my shadow ♪
♪ A notion growing inside ♪
♪ Now all the others seem shallow ♪
♪ All this running around ♪
♪ Bearing down on my shoulders ♪
♪ I can hear an alarm ♪
♪ It must be morning ♪
♪ I heard about a whirlwind
that's coming 'round ♪
♪ It's gonna carry off all
that isn't bound, and ♪
♪ When it happens, when it happens ♪
♪ I won't be holding on ♪
♪ So let it happen, let it happen ♪
♪ All this running around ♪
♪ I can't fight it much longer ♪
♪ Something's tryin' to get out ♪
♪ And it's never been closer ♪
♪ If my take-off fails ♪
♪ Make up some other story ♪
♪ But if I never come back ♪
♪ Tell my mother I'm sorry ♪
♪ I will not vanish and
you will not scare me ♪
♪ Try to get through it,
try to bounce to it ♪
♪ You were not thinkin'
that I will not do it ♪
♪ They be loving someone
and I'm not that stupid ♪
♪ Take the next ticket
to take the next train ♪
♪ Why would I do it? And
you wanna think that ♪
♪ I will not vanish and
you will not scare me ♪
♪ Try to get through it,
try to bounce to it ♪
♪ You were not thinkin'
that I will not do it ♪
♪ Oh, I'm ready for the
moment and the sound ♪
♪ Oh, but maybe I was ready all along ♪
♪ Oh, I'm ready for the
moment and the sound ♪
♪ Oh, but maybe I was ready all along ♪
♪ Oh baby, now I'm ready, moving on ♪
♪ Oh, baby ♪
(music fades)